[{"answer": "my friend won't be offended. my friend's never offended. What'd you say your name was", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "my friend. Suits you, my friend", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Present tense, please. Love her. Whatever she is. I'm thinking of her now, my friend. Will you think of her too", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Want you to do something, my friend", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Hurling's a fast game, isn't it, my friend", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Faster than cricket", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Cricket's in the halfpenny place", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You won't run", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "You fucking promised", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "You fucking did", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Do you miss him", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I think you do", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Maybe", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Did he dance with you", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Off his wages", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "He wants to know do I mean that", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "He wants to know do I mean that", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Bloody right I do..", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "You could", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Sure I do", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Ask me to meet you again, my friend", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Nothing's wise", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "How", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Will you meet me again", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Absolutely", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Are you pretending yet", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Yes", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "No, what is the thing", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "But you know what the thing is, my friend", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You vanished quite effectively. Became Mister Nobody. And you've no idea how useful that could be", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "We've got some plans here. And we'll need a Mister Nobody to execute them", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You're never out, my friend", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "What was it", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend, is it? Do you know me, my friend", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "So it was you all the time", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I thought it was my friend", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "I thought it was my friend", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "He's at home", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "And what happens then", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "And what if you don't", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "We'll be on the other side. We'll move when you do", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "my friend, I think you don't trust me", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "No", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I promise", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "What pills", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "What condition", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "You didn't", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "You tried", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "Tell me you love me", "docId": "Crying-Game.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Then say it", "qsentId": 50}]